<content>
  <section name="Welcome" des="Everything you need to know about what this webapp is and why it was made">
    <row>
      <subtitle>Welcome</subtitle>
      <p>Welcome to our site! Here we aim to connect women of all circumstances to appropriate abortion, contraception, or child-bearing resources.</p>
      <p>This site also serves as an educational resources on abortion and its alternatives, and why people may choose to get an abortion or not.</p>
      <p>Lastly, this site allows people to donate to multiple different abortion aid organizations.</p>
      <p>You can click on a section header above to get started. Hover over a section header to get an idea of what the section talks about.</p>
    </row>
    <row>
      <subtitle>Rationale</subtitle>
      <p>The mission of this site is simple: to connect women to whatever resources they may need when they decide to get an abortion or keep their pregnancy. But why launch this site now? Well, the US government (as of early 2017) has reimplemented the "gag rule." This rule prevents federally funded doctors from discussing abortion with their patients. They cannot tell women where to get abortions from, nor can they provide information on the procedure itself.</p>
      <p>That's where our mission comes in. This site isn't federally funded, so it's unaffected by the gag rule. Its purpose is to fill the role that doctors usually would. The internet is a powerful tool that can be leveraged to distribute information, so why not use it to counteract the gag rule? If enough women learn of this site's mission, then the gag rule will lose its potency.</p>
    </row>
    <row>
      <subtitle>Want to help?</subtitle>
      <p>If you find a bug, have a suggestion or want to write more content for this site, please email me at alugocp@aim.com</p>
    </row>
  </section>
  <section name="What is Abortion?" des="A rundown of what abortion is and isn't, why it's necessary, its alternatives, and the difference between pro-life and pro-choice">
    <row>
      <subtitle>A Definition</subtitle>
      <p>Abortion is the act of terminating one's pregnancy. There are a few different ways to get an abortion. The kind of abortion you get will depend on how long you've been pregnant. Medical abortions can be done in the first 13 weeks of pregnancy, but require multiple follow-up visits to your abortion clinic. Surgical abortions (which are more common than medical abortions) are performed anywhere from 13 to 23 weeks within the pregnancy. Surgical abortions involve using a suction tube to remove fetus tissue from your uterus. Abortions after 24 weeks of pregnancy are only performed when the fetus is severely disfigured, or if the mother's life is put at risk from her pregnancy.</p>
    </row>
    <row>
      <subtitle>Misconceptions</subtitle>
      <p>Abortion is not the murder of children. It is typically not performed after 24 weeks into a pregnancy, and pregnancies last 38 weeks on average. That means abortions are only performed during the first 2 out of 3 trimesters (The three time periods of a woman's pregnancy, each lasting around 12 weeks). The second trimester ends long before a fetus is fully developed. Abortions that do happen after 24 weeks are only done to save the mother's life. Pregnancy is a very complicated process, and can often put the mother at risk of death. Abortion is necessary in these situations, even if it is performed after the second trimester.</p>
    </row>
    <row col="2">
      <subtitle>Pro-Life vs. Pro-Choice</subtitle>
      <col>
        <p>Pro-life means you believe abortion should be outlawed. No matter the situation, a woman who is pregnant must go through with the pregnancy. Oftentimes people choose to be pro-life for religious reasons or because they fear people will use abortion as a form of contraception (they think people will purposefully have unprotected sex and then use abortion to terminate their pregnancy).</p>
      </col>
      <col>
        <p>Pro-choice means you believe abortions should be legal, and that women should be able to choose whether or not they have an abortion. People usually choose to be pro-choice because they understand that many pregnancies are a result of rape, can result in the mother's death, or that the parent(s) may not be able to take care of the child.</p>
      </col>
    </row>
    <row>
      <subtitle>Alternatives to Abortion</subtitle>
      <p>Unfortunately there aren't many alternatives to abortion. The most obvious/frequently used alternatives are listed below.</p><br></br>
      <p><b>• Contraception:</b> If you haven't become pregnant yet, then consider using this preventive alternative to abortion. Contraception comes in many forms, condoms being the cheapest, easiest and most readily available. Other forms of contraception includes birth control pills, spermicides, implants, sponges and diaphragms. If you can avoid an unwanted pregnancy by using contraception, then you won't need an abortion to begin with. The main downside to contraception is that most current methods involve a shot or implant, or mess with a woman's hormone levels.</p><br></br>
      <p><b>• Adoption:</b> Pro-life supporters believe abortion isn't neccessary because we have adoption. While it is a valid alternative to abortion, it doesn't work in all cases. If complications in a woman's pregnancy put her at increased risk of death, then adoption is not plausible. If the mother feels she will not be able to cope with giving up her child to adoption, then adoption is not plausible. This only becomes a viable option when the mother's pregnancy is healthy and she is willing to give her child up for adoption.</p>
    </row>
    <row>
      <subtitle>Why Are Abortions Necessary?</subtitle>
      <p>At first abortion may seem like a terrible idea, why would someone ever abort a pregnancy? Well, abortions are in fact quite necessary. Abortions give women control over unwanted or potentially fatal pregnancies. Some women cannot afford to take care of a child or to even be pregnant for a full 9 months. Maternal leave in the United States isn't on par with its European counterpart. A woman in her later stages of pregnancy is (in many cases) unable to come in to work for months at a time, and paid maternal leave in the US doesn't cover that long of an absence.</p><br></br>
      <p>Another reason someone would want to abort their pregnancy is because the pregnancy may kill them. Pregnancy really is one of the most beautiful, complex biological processes on our planet. Because of its complexity however, it can be complicated by scores of different factors. Even if a mother has no history whatsoever of alcohol, drugs or tobacco, her own body may negatively affect her pregnancy. Maybe she has a genetic mutation that affects the functionality of her uterus? Many women do. In many cases, these complications can negatively affect the fetus's development. They may end in death for the fetus, the mother, or even both. The only way to avoid these tragedies caused by the complications of birth is to abort one's pregnancy.</p><br></br>
      <p>Lastly, many women who become pregnant didn't even intend on having a child. Unfortunately it doesn't take consent to fertilize an egg, rape can impregnate a woman too. Rape is a terrible occurance in our modern time, and until it stops completely abortions will be a necessity for women around the world. You could tell couples to control their sexuality and avoid unwanted pregnancies, but abortions would still be necessary simply because of rape, economic strain, and complications of birth. For any of you who are religious, I suggest you pray to end these burdens instead of attacking abortion.</p>
    </row>
  </section>
  <section name="The Choice" des="A preliminary guide to help you make an informed decision on whether you should get an abortion or choose an alternative">
    <row>
      <subtitle>How do I decide?</subtitle>
      <p>There are many factors that go into your decision. Every situation is a little different, so I've created this site to help you come to the decision that you feel comfortable with. A good way to make a decision is to organize your information. Come to a conclusion based on the factors that affect your personal situation. This section of the site will walk you through some of the factors you should or shouldn't consider when deciding about an abortion.</p>
    </row>
    <row>
      <subtitle>Factors in Your Decision </subtitle>
      <p><b>• Pregnancy Health:</b> A major factor in your decision should be the health of your pregnancy. If your pregnancy is unhealthy (if it puts you at an abnormally high risk of death), then it may be wise to get an abortion.</p>
      <p><b>• Cause of pregnancy</b> Was this pregnancy intended or not? If it wasn't, you may want to consider getting an abortion.</p>
      <p><b>• Money:</b> In an ideal world, money truly wouldn't be a factor. Whether you wanted to get the abortion or keep your pregnancy, you'd be able to pay for it. Unfortunately however, this isn't an ideal world. Many women are forced into a decision regarding their pregnancy because they cannot afford to take care of a child or to have an abortion. Inadequate maternal leave will often push women towards getting an abortion. It's my hope that this site connects you with adequate funding so money no longer plays a part in your decision.</p>
      <p><b>• Yourself:</b> The most important factor in your decision is yourself. What do you really want to do with your pregnancy? Are you ready to have a child, or would you rather wait? Even though this site is supposed to help you understand your choices, you should ultimately decide to do what <b>you</b> want to do ith your pregnancy. If you feel like you can't decide, ask an friend or relative who's not biased about abortion. If you don't know anyone without a bias, call an abortion hotline. You can find their numbers in the Aid Services section. Good luck with your decision!</p>
    </row>
    <row>
      <subtitle>Non-factors</subtitle>
      <p><b>• Religion:</b> Religion should not affect your decision to have an abortion or not. You are the mother. You are the one who may be at increased risk of death. It is your decision, not the decision of your religious leader(s) or peers.</p>
      <!--<p><b>• Other people's Opinions:</b> Women who consider abortion are often confronted by their peers. People in a woman's life may not want her to get an abortion (usually because of religious reasons). If you are considering an abortion, you don't always need to listen to these people's opinions. If you're in a healthy relationship then it would be advised to discuss abortion with your boyfriend, but other than that you don't need to consider outside opinions very much. If you can't decide on your own, find a friend or family member who's unbiased to discuss abortion with. You can even talk to abortion specialists by calling a hotline (those can be found in the aid services section).</p>-->
    </row>
    <row>
      <subtitle>Once you've decided</subtitle>
      <p>After you've decided on what to do with your pregnancy, the next step is to seek aid (assuming you're in need of monetary support). The next section will show you multiple links to different abortion-related and birth-related aid websites and provide a quick description of what each one has to offer.</p>
    </row>
  </section>
  <section name="Aid Services" des="Various helpful resources you can access, no matter what you choose to do with your pregnancy">
    <row col="2">
      <col>
        <subtitle>Finding Abortion Funds</subtitle>
        <p>• <info href="https://abortionfunds.org/need-abortion/">Abortion Funds</info> has a map and a list of many US and a few international abortion funds.</p>
      </col>
      <col>
        <subtitle>Finding Abortion Clinics</subtitle>
        <div>• <info href="https://abortionfunds.org/how-do-i-find-the-clinic-thats-right-for-me/">Abortion Funds</info> gives helpful tips on finding a good abortion clinic, and warns against <b>fake clinics</b>.</div>
        <div>• <info href="https://www.abortioncarenetwork.org/abortion-care-providers/">Abortion Care Network</info> gives a list of abortion clinics around the country.</div>
        <div>• <info href="https://abortionclinics.com/">Abortion clinics.com</info> gives a list of abortion clinics by state and even city within the US. It also lists some Canadian and international abortion clinics.</div>
        <br></br>
        <p><b>Disclaimer: </b>Keep in mind these sites don't list every abortion clinic in the country.</p>
      </col>
    </row>
    <row>
      <subtitle>Hotlines</subtitle>
      <p>• <b>1-800-772-9100:</b> National Abortion Federation's hotline for getting unbiased abortion-related information, including financial assistance.</p>
      <p>• <b>1-877-257-0012:</b> National Abortion Federation's hotline. Provides referrals for abortion providers.</p>
    </row>
  </section>
  <section name="Donate" des="Instructions on how to donate to various aid services">
    <row>
      <subtitle>Donate to an Abortion Fund</subtitle>
      <p>Below you'll find links to the donation pages of several abortion funds around the country. Many of these sites use their own scripting to generate donation keys, so it's easier to just link you to their main page and tell you where to look to find the donation links.</p><br></br>
      <div>• <info href="https://www.plannedparenthood.org">Planned Parenthood</info>: Look in the upper right corner of their website and you'll find their donation link.</div>
      <div>• <info href="https://abortionfunds.org">Abortion Funds</info>: Look to your right and you'll find a donation link.</div>
      <div>• <info href="https://www.abortioncarenetwork.org/donation/">Abortion Care Network</info>: This one's actually a direct link to their donations page :D</div>
      <div>• <info href="https://prochoice.org/about-naf/support-naf/">National Abortion Federation</info>: Links you directly to their donations page.</div>
    </row>
  </section>
  <section name="Credits" des="Recognizing the people who helped make this project happen">
    <row>
      <subtitle>Programming</subtitle>
      <p>Alex Lugo</p>
    </row>
    <row col="2">
      <col>
        <subtitle>Writers</subtitle>
        <p>Alex Lugo</p>
      </col>
      <col>
        <subtitle>Editors</subtitle>
        <p>Hibba Hussain</p>
        <p>Leah Duff</p>
      </col>
    </row>
    <row>
      <subtitle>Featured Aid Services</subtitle>
      <info href="https://www.plannedparenthood.org/">Planned Parenthood</info>
      <info href="https://abortionfunds.org">Abortion Funds</info>
      <info href="https://www.abortioncarenetwork.org/">Abortion Care Network</info>
      <info href="https://abortionclinics.com/">Abortion clinics.com</info>
      <info href="https://prochoice.org/">National Abortion Federation</info>
    </row>
  </section>
</content>
